(smooth hip hop music)
♪ So hot in, hot in, hot in ♪
♪ So hot in here,
so hot in here ♪
♪ So hot in, so hot in, hot in ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Wanna a little bit o' ♪
♪ Wanna little bit o' ah, ah ♪
♪ And a little bit o' ♪
♪ Check a little bit o' ♪
♪ Just a little bit o',
just a little bit o' ♪
♪ Just a little bit o' ♪
♪ I was like, good gracious
ass is bodacious, uh ♪
♪ Flirtatious, tryin'
to show faces, ah ♪
♪ Lookin' for the right time
to shoot my steam, you know ♪
♪ Lookin' for the right
time to flash them keys ♪
♪ Then, um, I'm leavin',
please believin', oh ♪
♪ Me and the rest
of my heathens ♪
♪ Check it, got it locked at
the top of the Four Seasons ♪
♪ Penthouse, roof
top, birds I feedin' ♪
♪ No deceivin', nothin' up
my sleeve and no teasin' ♪
♪ I need you to get up
up on the dance floor ♪
♪ Give that man
what he askin' for ♪
♪ 'Cause I feel
like bustin' loose ♪
♪ And I feel like
touchin' you, uh, uh ♪
♪ And can't nobody
stop the juice ♪
♪ So baby tell me
what's the use ♪
♪ I said ♪
♪ It's gettin' hot
in here, so hot ♪
♪ So take off all your clothes ♪
♪ Oh, I am gettin' so hot ♪
♪ I wanna take my clothes off ♪
♪ Uh, uh, uh, uh, oh ♪
♪ It's gettin' hot
in here, so hot ♪
♪ So take off all your clothes ♪
♪ Eh, I am gettin' so hot ♪
♪ I wanna take my clothes off ♪
♪ Uh, uh, Nelly hang all out ♪
♪ Why you at the bar if you
ain't poppin' the bottles ♪
♪ Come on, what good is all the
fame if you ain't, uh,
the models ♪
♪ I see you drivin' sports car
ain't hittin' the throttle ♪
♪ And I be down, and do a
hundred, top down and goggles ♪
♪ Get off the freeway,
exit 106 and parked it ♪
♪ Ash tray, flipped
it, time to spark it ♪
♪ Gucci collar for dollar,
got out and walked it ♪
♪ I spit game 'cause
baby I can't talk it ♪
♪ Warm, uh, sweatin', uh,
it's hot up in this joint ♪
♪ Vokal, tanktop, all
on at this point ♪
♪ You're with a winner
so baby you can't lose ♪
♪ I got secrets,
can't leave Cancun ♪
♪ So take it off like
you're home alone ♪
♪ You know dance in
front the mirror ♪
♪ While you're on the phone ♪
♪ Checkin' your reflection
and tellin' your best friend ♪
♪ Like, girl I think my
butt gettin' big, oh ♪
♪ It's gettin' hot
in here, so hot ♪
♪ So take off all
your clothes, eh ♪
♪ I am gettin' so hot ♪
♪ I wanna take my clothes off ♪
♪ Uh, uh, uh, uh, oh ♪
♪ It's gettin' hot
in here, so hot ♪
♪ So take off all
your clothes, eh ♪
♪ I am gettin' so hot ♪
♪ I wanna take my clothes off ♪
♪ Uh, uh, Nelly hang all out ♪
♪ Mix a little bit o' uh, uh ♪
♪ With a little bit o' uh,
uh, Nelly just fall out ♪
♪ Give a little bit o' uh, uh ♪
♪ With a little bit o' uh, uh ♪
♪ Nelly hang all out ♪
♪ And a sprinklin' o' uh,
uh, Nelly just fall out ♪
♪ I like it when you uh, uh ♪
♪ Girl, baby make
it uh, uh, oh ♪
- Hold up, hold up!
(crowd shouting over each other)
Oh no, the roof!
The roof, the roof is on fire!
♪ The roof, the roof,
the roof is on fire ♪
♪ We don't need no water,
let the mother burn, burn ♪
♪ Burn, mother, burn ♪
♪ Burn ♪
♪ Oh, stop placin',
time wastin' ♪
♪ I got a friend with
a pole in a basement ♪
- What?
♪ I'm just kiddin' like Jason ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Unless you goin' do it ♪
♪ Extra, extra, eh, spread
the news, check it ♪
♪ Nelly took a trip from
the Luna to Neptune ♪
♪ Came back with
somethin' thicker than
fittin' in Sassoons ♪
♪ Say she like to think
about cuttin' in restrooms ♪
♪ Oh, it's gettin'
hot in here, so hot ♪
♪ So take off all
your clothes, eh ♪
♪ I am gettin' so hot ♪
♪ I wanna take my clothes off ♪
♪ Uh, uh, uh, uh, oh ♪
♪ It's gettin' hot
in here, so hot ♪
♪ So take off all
your clothes, eh ♪
♪ I am gettin' so
hot, check it ♪
♪ I wanna take my clothes off ♪
♪ Uh, uh, Nelly hang all out ♪
♪ It's gettin' hot
in here, so hot ♪
♪ So take off all
your clothes, eh ♪
♪ I am gettin' so hot,
bring it, bring it ♪
♪ I wanna take my clothes off ♪
♪ Bring the bridge back ♪
♪ Nelly hang all out, mix
a little bit o' uh, uh ♪
♪ With a little bit o' uh,
uh, Nelly just fall out ♪
♪ Give a little bit o' uh, uh ♪
♪ With a little bit o' uh,
uh, Nelly hang all out ♪
♪ With a little bit o' uh, uh ♪
And a sprinklin' o' uh,
uh, Nelly just fall out
♪ I like it when ya uh, uh ♪
♪ Girl, baby make it uh, uh ♪
♪ Oh ♪